

# **Muhammad Noman**

MERN Stack Developer

I am a Full Stack MERN Developer with proficiency and expertise in all aspects of Front-End and Back-End development. I have been working full-time for the past two years, and during development, I try my best to follow best practices ( DRY and SOLID ) and Software Development specifications. I am a collaborative and easy-to-work-with type of person. I am an excellent problem solver and a fast learner to implement complex and creative solutions daily.

#### $\times$

nomanshk310@gmail.com



+92310-7497393



Faisalabad, Pakistan



linkedin.com/in/muhammadnoman-8b8092232



https://join.skype.com/invite/ ysbrDne4X1hp



github.com/Noman-Sheikh-09

#### **SKILLS**

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

ReactJs

Redux

Graphal

Novt le

Eirobaca

React Native

MongoDb

NodeJs

ExpressJs

RestAPI

# **LANGUAGES**

#### English

Limited Working Proficiency

#### Hrdi

Full Professional Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Programming

Sports

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Jr React Developer Techloset Solution

08/2022 - 05/2023

# MERN Stack Developer Fiverr

01/2022 - Present

### MERN Stack Developer LabD IT Solution

03/2024 - Present

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bs(Computer Science)**Government College University Faisalabad

09/2020 - Present Faisalabad

# **PROJECTS**

#### Social Estate

Front-end: https://github.com/Noman-Sheikh-09/Social-Estate-Client
Back-end: https://github.com/Noman-Sheikh-09/Server-Social-estate

#### Sale Street

- □ Front-end: https://github.com/Noman-Sheikh-09/sale-street
- Back-end: https://github.com/Noman-Sheikh-09/sale-street-server
- $\hbox{$\square$ Dashboard: https://github.com/Noman-Sheikh-09/sale-street-admin}$

## Easy Server

- □ Front-end: https://github.com/Noman-Sheikh-09/easy-serve
- $\hbox{$\blacksquare$ Back-end: $https://github.com/Noman-Sheikh-09/easy-serve-server}$
- □ Dashboard: https://github.com/Noman-Sheikh-09/easy-serve-admin

#### Doctoryab Dr Portal (React Native)

- Worked on Both front-end & back-end of this application
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.microcis.doctor\_yab

#### Doctoryab

- Worked on back-end of this Application
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=app.doctoryab.panel

#### Admin Panel for Doctoryab & Doctoryab Dr Portal

Worked on both front-end & back-end of this portal

#### Property Selling App

Worked on front-end of this App in React Native